For everyone that takes time to come and tell folks who are trying to take action
why their action is a waste of time or why their action is not the right action,
but who never can offer up another action, save your energy.
You are being contrarian. Okay. When things are extreme, you need to counter with extreme.
Gun violence in America is extreme. When you see me say things like there needs to be a gun buyback
program and you say, well, no, what we need to do is, what we need to do is, and you address like
esoteric things. Like we need to work on masculinity. We need to work on mental health.
Yes. But there are also practical applications that can be done that are the counter to the
extreme that's happening. The basic physics of things is that to every action, there's equal
and opposite reaction. Drastic change requires drastic change. And for all the black folks
saying, well, if they take our guns, then what are we going to do when they come for us?
Baby, they've already come for us. What are you doing with your guns right now?